[{"question_text": "Capacit\u00e9s sportives", "answer": "Individual_answer", "color_hex": "#5356a5", "answer_id": "strength_i", "paths": ["M73.19,165.46c12.33,9.83,24.75,13,39.79,16.68,3,.72,6,1.6,8.4,3.56s3.85,5.28,2.81,8.16c-1.41,3.89-6.25,5-10.35,5.59-13.83,1.92-27.52,3-40.61,8.06A116,116,0,0,0,42,225.65c-18.57,15-32.7,35.79-38.67,59-11.19,43.49,6.78,93,43.25,119.17s89.11,27.39,126.74,2.9S231.13,333.63,222,289.67c-2.21-10.58-6-21.31-4-31.95,3.84-21.18,28.23-32.13,49.73-33s43.28,4.75,64.39.58c32.21-6.37,57.59-37.71,57.12-70.54S362.39,91.36,330,85.93c-17.15-2.88-33.56,1.66-48.29,10.21-13.78,8-21.41,18.74-28.17,33.08-6.38,13.53-13.08,28.2-25.93,36.82-3.22,2.16-7.29,3.39-11,2.39s-6.89-4.65-6.48-8.51c.23-2.14,1.45-4,2.63-5.84,11-16.74,20.45-34.44,20.45-55.13,2.11-48.68-33.94-90.3-81.58-97.8a91,91,0,0,0-29.78.16C75.32,9.45,38.31,55.66,41.25,102.88A88.47,88.47,0,0,0,64.4,157.33,81.48,81.48,0,0,0,73.19,165.46Z"]}, {"question_text": "Palmar\u00e8s", "answer": "Individual_answer", "color_hex": "#000000", "answer_id": "palmares_i", "paths": ["M345.34,354.88a50.27,50.27,0,0,0-1.93-6.32c-3.43-9.07-10-17.91-18.27-23.1-7.05-4.4-16.92-4.13-19.31-13.63-1.2-4.79,15.32-9.41,18.44-11.49,7.56-5,13-14,15.06-22.71,3.75-16.05-3.42-31.55-15.54-41.93-17.66-15.13-45.55-22.9-71.47-18.2-14,2.55-27,8.65-29.13,5.06-1.2-2,6.71-17.43,7.67-20.08,3-8.4,5.87-16.87,8.41-25.43,5.32-17.93,9.59-36.39,10.8-55.1,2.16-33.53-13-79.75-54.12-77.52-17.89,1-31,12.9-42.52,25.5-12,13.17-14.88,24-20.33,23.26-7.35-1-5.66-21-15.65-43.31C107.11,26.84,83-.49,58.65,0,37.37.44,23,20.63,14.92,38-3.65,77.89-3.61,124.06,8,165.86c4.79,17.2,10.79,34.67,20.86,49.57,5,7.43,11.12,14.32,18.75,19.16,8.23,5.22,17.82,5.32,25,12.16,2.54,26.34-3.67,54.34,18.44,75.07C108.7,337.17,126,347,150.7,331.06c12.65-11.1,13.75-12.39,26.38-.48,9.93,7.16,21.73,7.94,33.48,8.72,12.53.83,18.93-1.11,20.59,2.14,1.89,3.71-6.85,16.51-7.44,21.3a52.36,52.36,0,0,0,5.09,29.65c12.66,25.17,47.66,38.12,74.13,30C330.92,413.89,352.12,384,345.34,354.88ZM83.82,175c-1.72,19.26-20.53,13.49-27.15-.17C38.26,148.55,27.14,64.55,48,38.71c10.07-7.44,22.3,5.45,26.17,13.83,4.19,9.1,4.91,19.3,6.42,29.07C85.57,112.5,88.45,143.85,83.82,175Zm101.65,8.87c-5.71,17.6-48.3,134.29-70.48,117.41-24.47-19,33.64-142.5,49-165.9,6.1-12.16,22-41.85,36-21.8C207.21,127.39,189.38,167.14,185.47,183.86ZM255.4,288.6c-13.55,6.67-28.56,11.6-43.75,12-24.87-.52-10.32-22,3.73-27.54,20.54-10.2,46.94-22.06,70.12-19.44C301.21,261.85,263,285.15,255.4,288.6ZM296.85,376c-25.53,32.31-38.46,9.44-20.07-18C293.34,335.46,312.39,356.36,296.85,376Z"]}, {"question_text": "Ville souvenir", "answer": "Tokyo", "color_hex": "#ef4136", "answer_id": "city_tokyo", "paths": ["M254.87,116.19C235.42-55.84-2.39-28.43.14,143c-3.43,58.34,59,93.68,97.31,42.91,18.83-26,5.06-60.71,12.6-90.13,9.14-24.18,40.12-8.29,38.94,13.54,2.41,23.83-7.39,48.46-.72,71.47,9.66,36.41,59,49.6,85.51,22.8C255.77,181,256.15,145.81,254.87,116.19Z"]}, {"question_text": "Personalit\u00e9 sportive", "answer": "Audacieux", "color_hex": "#62b0e4", "answer_id": "personalitly_audacieux", "paths": ["M253.13,124.42c-4.3-25.69-36.81-41.16-57.73-24-4.4,4.47-13.23,11.32-18,3.79-1.87-4.51,2.58-6.59,5.86-7.69C206.85,91,225.1,66.12,210.83,43.2,188,12.71,149.94,31.15,149,66.88,146.24,76,134.63,80.52,132,68.54c-1.19-17.5,15.66-27.32,4.71-47.73C126.11-.66,95.75-6.31,76.92,7.58,50.63,25.44,55.82,68.87,85.62,80c5.29,2.13,11.67,3.72,14,8.91a9.18,9.18,0,0,1-4.29,11.63c-10.48,4.33-24.75-18.46-46.74-17.89C18.68,81.91-4.73,114.25.82,142.76c8.4,42.38,60.46,50.74,81.52,12.76,18.16-21.42,33.24-2.23,23.52,18.95-34.08,70.79,72.87,91.24,81.68,20.06C189,171.11,172.94,164,158,150.86c-10.17-9.12,1.1-20.82,10.52-11.53,7,12.39,10.66,27.52,24.53,34.68C224.39,194,261,157,253.13,124.42Z"]}, {"question_text": "R\u00e9action face \u00e0 l'\u00e9chec", "answer": "E\u0301nerve\u0301.e", "color_hex": "#64a744", "answer_id": "failure_enerve", "paths": ["M337.36,134.41c-1.07-24.29-21.87-38.46-41-49.48C249.64,57.72,203,27,155.13,1.37c-16.5-5.41-34,5.84-36.36,23-3.06,17,5.74,34.88,14.91,48.63A303.53,303.53,0,0,1,94.84,46.81C71,28.5,46.28-9,12.16,8.48c-14,9.11-15.48,25.41-6.63,38.88,9.07,13.78,24.6,21.24,36.6,32.17q34.81,27.25,71.76,51.59c18,10.49,33.88,26.84,55.23,29.9,29.29,2.7,40.75-25.88,27-49.14,0-1.1-11.09-22.54-7-20.23,37.41,25.27,72.76,59.79,117.19,71.26C323.41,165.11,339.37,152,337.36,134.41Z"]}, {"question_text": "Origine", "answer": "Extraverti.e", "color_hex": "#fbe009", "answer_id": "introextra_extra", "paths": ["M252.3,124c-2.7-23.58-12.15-45.05-39.79-34.71-29.81,15.21-7.59,77.57-50.13,76.74-27.94-9.4-28.36-51-32.7-75.87-2.37-19.19-5.07-38.77-13.76-56C99.58-2.46,53.43-12.67,26.4,18.53,5.24,40.84-20.72,112,26.77,117.72c32.54-4,20.52-45.91,38.13-46.42,7.45,1,8.58,10,8.14,16.12-.53,27.3.78,55.16,10.26,80.76C120.77,276.37,265,230.43,252.3,124Z"]}, {"question_text": "Int\u00e9r\u00eat", "answer": "Individual_answer", "color_hex": NaN, "answer_id": "interest_i", "paths": [NaN]}, {"question_text": "Sens favori", "answer": "Toucher", "color_hex": "#5356a5", "answer_id": "senses_toucher", "paths": ["M123,0c6.71-.13,13.28,1.82,18.15,6.42,8.59,8.11,9.32,22,4.92,33s-12.93,19.67-21.24,28.06l-51.47,52c-4.26,4.29-8.61,8.74-10.9,14.34s-2,12.69,2.3,16.94,11.25,4.46,16.84,2.3,10.15-6.29,14.73-10.15a231.35,231.35,0,0,1,73.82-41.83c10.51-3.61,21.7-6.48,32.67-4.67s21.65,9.37,24,20.24c2,9.12-2.24,18.74-8.82,25.38s-15.21,10.77-23.82,14.38a303.88,303.88,0,0,1-85.9,21.94c-7.26.76-14.81,1.33-21.16,4.91s-11.11,11.23-8.83,18.16c1.75,5.32,7.17,8.77,12.68,9.79s11.17.05,16.69-.92L183.48,197c15-2.63,30.68-5.24,45.32-1s27.82,17.67,26.48,32.87c-1.22,13.88-14.13,24.46-27.71,27.59s-27.76.48-41.45-2.18L115,240.47c-5.61-1.09-11.42-2.18-17-.9s-10.86,5.62-11.37,11.32c-.83,9.48,10.46,14.78,19.64,17.27L190.42,291c10.6,2.87,21.5,5.9,30.16,12.65s14.58,18.25,11.51,28.78c-3,10.28-13.77,16.79-24.41,17.86s-21.23-2.26-31.24-6c-30.69-11.57-59.45-27.65-87.89-44C65.26,286.88,41.65,272.92,24,252.64,11,237.64,1.81,218.78.37,198.8s1.16-32.26,9.94-50.5A760.5,760.5,0,0,1,81.21,29.86C88.41,20,96.19,10,107,4.23A35.88,35.88,0,0,1,123,0Z"]}, {"question_text": "\u00c9l\u00e9ment favori", "answer": "Eau", "color_hex": "#4e8cca", "answer_id": "element_eau", "paths": ["M193.86,184.1c-4.76-23.8-20.31-43.29-30.76-64.88a159.19,159.19,0,0,1-11.4-105.6C152.94,8.47,153.06,1,147.85.08c-4.3-.76-7.19,4.16-8.83,8.21C102.72,114-14,117.26,1.39,210.19,23.49,337.34,213,315.37,193.86,184.1Z"]}, {"question_text": "Devise", "answer": "Plus loin", "color_hex": "#231f20", "answer_id": "direction_loin", "paths": ["M311.84,12.22C303-24.69,222.11,33.09,201.28,40.4c-15.79,10.82-32.12-1.36-49,.7-34.89,4.39-32.41,28.27-47.2,33.92-9.06-.48-15-9.67-23.63-12.3a47.73,47.73,0,0,0-50.18,8C19.23,81.17-13.46,125,6.1,137.42c5.36,3.22,12.41,2.66,17.93-.27,6.41-3.4,10.22-9.14,13.86-15.14,31.09-50.6,38.66,9.88,84.48-13.89,5.9-2.93,12-6.79,15.87-12.07,17.52-22,41,6.62,82.64-14.9,15-6,29.05-14.09,43.05-22.15C280.45,49.17,315.79,35.47,311.84,12.22Z"]}, {"question_text": "Dessin du succ\u00e8s", "answer": "Individual_answer", "color_hex": NaN, "answer_id": "success_i", "paths": [NaN]}]